Guide to the Tiger's Eye Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series I: Correspondence, [1939]-1955; 12; (29 boxes)
  - Correspondence regarding subscriptions
    - Correspondence - July to December, 1947, 3 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - January 1948, 1947-1948; 5 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - February 1948, 1947-1948; 4 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - March 1948, 1947-1948; 5 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - April 1948, 5 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - May 1948, 1947-1948; 5 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - June 1948, 5 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - July 1948, 1947-1949; 5 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - August 1948, 1947-1949; 5 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - September 1948, 4 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - October 1948, 1947-1948; 5 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - November 1948, 1947-1949; 7 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - December 1948, 1947-1949; 5 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - January 1949, 1948-1949; 5 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - February 1949, 1948-1949; 4 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - March 1949, 1948-1949; 3 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - April 1949, 1948-1949; 4 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - May 1949, 5 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - June 1949, 1948-1949; 4 (Box 19)
    - Correspondence - July 1949, 5 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence - August 1949, 5 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence - September 1949, 4 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence - October 1949, 1948-1949; 5 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence - November 1949, 4 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence - December 1949, 4 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence - January 1950, 1949-1950; 3 (Box 20)
    - Filled orders - subscribers, 1947-1948; 3 (Box 21)
    - Subscription bills - unpaid, 1947 (Box 21)
    - List of early subscribers, 1947-1948 (Box 21)
    - Subscriber index cards, undated; 5 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1951 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence with subscription agents
    - American News Company, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 22)
    - Berkhardt, W. Patrick, 1949, 1951 (Box 22)
    - Cassell Publishers Service (New Jersey), 1948, 1951 (Box 22)
    - Cassell Subscription Agency (Illinois), 1948 (Box 22)
    - Cellar Book Shop Subscription Agency, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - Clark Subscription Agency (Helen Pierson), 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Crowley The Magazine Man, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 22)
    - E. W. Wallis Magazine Agency, 1948 (Box 22)
    - F. W. Faxon Co. (Boston), 1947-1951; 2 (Box 22)
    - Franklin Square Subscription Agency (New York, New Jersey), 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Hanson-Bennett Magazine Agency, 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Herman Goldberger Agency, 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Moore-Cottrell Subscription Agencies, 1947-1951 (Box 22)
    - Slade, R. E., 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Subscription House, Inc., 1949 February (Box 22)
    - Turner Subscription Agency, 1948-1951 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence with booksellers
    - A. B. Sandbergs Bokhandel, 1949-1950 (Box 22)
    - A. G. Comings & Son, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - A & W Head, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - Albert Bonnier Publishing House, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - Argos (Spain), 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Athena Bookshop, 1949, 1951 (Box 22)
    - Barrett Bookstore, 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - Beekman Place Bookstore, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - Bennett & Marshall Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - Bennington College Cooperative Store, 1947-1948 (Box 22)
    - Betty Parsons Gallery, 1947-1951 (Box 22)
    - Blair's Bookshop, 1947-1951 (Box 22)
    - Blanke, J. M., 1947-1948 (Box 22)
    - The Blue Door (Emanuel Berg), 1948-1950 (Box 22)
    - Bogue Book Co., 1948-1950 (Box 22)
    - The Book & Print Shop, 1947-1948 (Box 22)
    - The Book Box, 1948-1950 (Box 22)
    - The Book Center, 1948-1950 (Box 22)
    - Book Clearing House, 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - The Book Corner, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - The Book Mark, 1948-1951 (Box 22)
    - The Book Shelf, 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - The Book Shop (Davenport, Iowa), 1948 (Box 22)
    - The Book Shop (Iowa City, Iowa), 1948 (Box 22)
    - The Book Shop (Providence, Rhode Island), 1947-1951 (Box 22)
    - The Book Shop (Sackin, Lawrence), 1948 (Box 22)
    - The Bookery (Denver, Colorado), 1948 (Box 22)
    - The Bookery (Mansfield, Ohio), 1948-1949 (Box 22)
    - Bookman's, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Books on Telegraph Hill, 1948-1950 (Box 23)
    - The Bookworm, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Brentano's (Beverly Hills), 1949 May (Box 23)
    - Brentano's (Hartford), 1947-1949 (Box 23)
    - Brentano's (New York), 1947-1950 (Box 23)
    - Brentano's (Los Angeles), 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Briggs, Harold E., 1947-1949 (Box 23)
    - Brody's Stationary & Gift Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 23)
    - Brown & Delphi, 1948-1951 (Box 23)
    - Brown Book Shop, 1948 (Box 23)
    - Bryant Park Newsstand, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Bryn Mawr College Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - California Book Co., Ltd., 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Campbell's Book Store, 1947-1949 (Box 23)
    - Canada - miscellaneous book stores, 1947-1949 (Box 23)
    - Cantabrigia Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Canyon Corners, 1947-1949 (Box 23)
    - Catskill Book & Record Shop, 1947-1951 (Box 23)
    - Clinton Book Store, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - College Book Shop (Palo Alto), 1948-1950 (Box 23)
    - College Book Store (State College), 1947-1950 (Box 23)
    - Columbia University Bookstore, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Colorado Springs Book Shop (Clauson, Henry), 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Concord Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Congress News Company, 1948-1950 (Box 23)
    - Contemporary Gallery, 1949-1950 (Box 23)
    - Courtesy News Company, 1947-1949 (Box 23)
    - Cyril's Studio Gallery, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Daliel's, 1947-1950 (Box 23)
    - Dauber & Pine Bookshops, Inc., 1948-1950 (Box 23)
    - Doubleday Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Dufour's Book Center, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - 8th Street Bookshop, Inc., 1948-1950 (Box 23)
    - Eastern News Company, 1948-1951 (Box 23)
    - Edith Farnsworth's Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - The Edward P. Judd Company, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - England - bookstores, 1933-1948 (Box 23)
    - 57th Street Book & Card Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - The 4J Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Faber, Inc. (Gotham Hotel News Stand), 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Fairfield Smoke Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 23)
    - Firma L. J. C. Boucher (Holland), 1948-1951 (Box 23)
    - Foreign - miscellaneous stores, 1948-1951 (Box 24)
    - Foster Book Company, 1948 (Box 24)
    - Fountain House Book Shop, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - Fountain News Company, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Four Season Book Shop, 1947-1951 (Box 24)
    - Frameshop Gallery, 1949-1950 (Box 24)
    - Galignani (France), 1948, 1950 (Box 24)
    - General News Agency, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Georgia Lingafelt - Books, 1947-1950 (Box 24)
    - The Georgian Book Shops, 1948-1950 (Box 24)
    - Gilmore - The News Man, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - Glenn, Robert C., 1949, 1951 (Box 24)
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1947-1951; 2 (Box 24)
    - Gottfried Brothers, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Groiler Book Shop, 1947-1950 (Box 24)
    - Guadalupe Art Gallery, 1947-1950 (Box 24)
    - The Hagedorn Book Shop, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 24)
    - Hanson & Johnson, 1947-1950 (Box 24)
    - Hartman, Harry, 1947-1950 (Box 24)
    - Hawkins Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Hayes, Harrison J., 1948 (Box 24)
    - Hedom Hall, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - House of the Artists, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - Human Affairs, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Immerman, S., 1948 (Box 24)
    - Indiana Theatre Magazine and News Shop, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - J. L. Hudson Co., 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - Kamin Dance Bookshop & Gallery, 1948-1949 (Box 24)
    - Ken Book Shop, 1948 (Box 24)
    - Kieser's Book Store, 1948-1951 (Box 24)
    - Klein's Stationary Store, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - Kroch's Bookstores, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - La Casa Belga (Havana, Cuba), 1948, 1950 (Box 24)
    - Latin America - miscellaneous book stores, 1947-1949 (Box 24)
    - The Louvre, 1948-1950 (Box 24)
    - Maxwell, Lawrence, 1947-1951 (Box 25)
    - McClelland's Bookstore, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - McEvoy, Caroline, 1950 (Box 25)
    - McMurray's Book Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Magabook Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Main Street Book Store, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Marriner's Book Store, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - Martin, Louis H., 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Martindale, W. L., 1947-1950 (Box 25)
    - Marsh's Book Store, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Marshall Field & Co., 1947-1949 (Box 25)
    - Mecham, Kathryn, 1949, 1951 (Box 25)
    - Metropolitan News Agency, 1947-1949 (Box 25)
    - Minnesota Book Shop, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Moby Dick Bookshop, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - Modern Ballet Center, 1947-1950 (Box 25)
    - Mohl, Leo, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Mosiman's Book Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Motive Book Shop (Crews, Judson), 1949 (Box 25)
    - Nebraska Book Co., 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - New Mexico Book Store, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - New York bookstores, 1947-1948; 2 (Box 25)
    - Nissen Book Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Nodelman's News Depot, 1948 February 26 (Box 25)
    - Normandy House Book Store, 1947-1950 (Box 25)
    - The Old Book Store, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - The Open Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - Otto Ulbrich Co., 1948-1951 (Box 25)
    - Park Book Shop, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Parnassus Bookshop, 1948-1951 (Box 25)
    - Pat Wall Gallery, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Paul Elder & Co., 1948-1951 (Box 25)
    - Paul Theobald & Co., 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Pen & Palette, 1947-1951 (Box 25)
    - Peoria News Store, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Peridot Gallery, 1949-1950 (Box 25)
    - The Personal Book Shop, 1948-1951 (Box 25)
    - Pirret Book & Stationery, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - The Print Club, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Publix Book Mart, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - Quadrangle Book Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - R. Gordon & Co., 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - R. M. Mills Book Store, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Rainbo Art Materials, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Ramage, Emily, 1947-1951 (Box 25)
    - The Red Door Book Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Red Quill Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - Red's News Stand, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Rengstorff Book Store, 1947-1949 (Box 25)
    - Roher's Bookshop (Canada), 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - Romaine, Paul, 1949-1950 (Box 25)
    - Rosengren, Frank, 1948-1950 (Box 25)
    - 750 Studio, 1948 (Box 26)
    - The Sather Gate Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 26)
    - Satyr Book Shop, 1947-1948 (Box 26)
    - The Sevenstairs, 1948-1950 (Box 26)
    - Siefert's Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 26)
    - Slater's, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 26)
    - Smith & McCance, 1947-1949 (Box 26)
    - Smith News Co., 1947-1949 (Box 26)
    - Spitzer Book Shop, 1948-1950 (Box 26)
    - Stechert-Hafner Inc., 1948-1951 (Box 26)
    - Stephens College Bookshop, 1947-1949 (Box 26)
    - Strong, Barbara, 1948, 1951 (Box 26)
    - Student Book Exchange, 1948-1950 (Box 26)
    - Sutton Manor Bookstore, 1948-1949 (Box 26)
    - Temple & Carroll, 1948 (Box 26)
    - Texarkana Book Store, 1948 (Box 26)
    - Three Arts Shop, 1948 (Box 26)
    - Tulsa Book Shop, 1947-1951 (Box 26)
    - The Union News Co., 1947-1949 (Box 26)
    - Universal News Agency, 1947-1949 (Box 26)
    - University Book Exchange, 1948-1950 (Box 26)
    - University Book Store, 1947-1951 (Box 26)
    - University of Chicago Bookstore, 1947-1949 (Box 26)
    - The Varsity Book Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop, 1948 (Box 27)
    - Vroman's Book Store, 1947-1948 (Box 27)
    - Washington Square Book Shop, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Weitz, Frank (The Eton Shops), 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Werk, M., 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Werner's Books Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 27)
    - Weyhe Art Books, 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Whitlocks Inc., 1948 (Box 27)
    - Whitman Book Shop of Philadelphia, 1948-1950 (Box 27)
    - Whyte Bookshop & Gallery, Inc., 1947-1950 (Box 27)
    - Wittenborn & Company, 1947-1951; 3 (Box 27)
    - Wolman, H., 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Woodworth's Bookstore, 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - World News Service, 1948-1950 (Box 27)
    - Yale Cooperative Corporation, 1947-1951 (Box 27)
    - Young Books, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - Younger News Store, 1948-1950 (Box 27)
    - Zeitlin and Ver Brugge, 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - Zibart Brothers Retail Stores, 1947-1950 (Box 27)
    - "A-C", 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - "D-F", 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - "G-I", 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - "J-L", 1947-1948 (Box 27)
    - "M-O", 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - "P-R", 1947-1950 (Box 27)
    - "S-U", 1947-1949 (Box 27)
    - "V-Z", 1947-1948 (Box 27)
    - Letters to bookstores (current), 1948-1949 (Box 27)
    - Foreign commerce information, 1949 (Box 27)
    - Bills to go out for Issue #6, 1949 March, undated (Box 27)
- Series II. Index Cards, [1947-1951]; 0.42; (2 boxes)
  Index cards consist of three separate index files. The largest is to the content of individual issues of the magazine.
  - Index to issues, [1947-1949] (Box 28)
  - Poetry Bulletin, undated (Box 29)
  - Advertising, [1947-1951] (Box 29)
- Series III. Manuscripts, 1947-1949; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  Arranged by issue.
  This series contains typescript or holograph drafts of textual content of issues 1-8. For issue 9, this material is present along with proofs and other material documenting production of that issue.
  - Issue #1, undated (Box 30)
  - Issue #2, 1947, undated; 3 (Box 30)
  - Issue #3, [1948]; 3 (Box 30)
  - Issue #4, [1948]; 3 (Box 30)
  - Issue #5, [1948]; 3 (Box 30)
  - Issue #6, [1947-1948]; 3 (Box 31)
  - Issue #7, [1948-1949]; 3 (Box 31)
  - Issue #8, [1949]; 3 (Box 31)
  - "Current issue", [1949]; 5 (Box 32)
  - "Current issue for printer", undated; 3 (Box 32)
  - Attaway, Hauser stories, undated (Box 32)
  - Approved advertisements, 1949 (Box 32)
  - Overmatter, undated
  - Tiger's Eye print copies, 1947, undated; 4 (Box 33)
  - Printer's copy, 1949 June; 3 (Box 33)
  - Page proofs - complete set, 1949 June, undated
  - Editorial notes, 1949 January 28, undated (Box 33)
- Series IV. Business Records, 1947-1951; 6.88; (18 boxes)
  Arranged according to original file headings.
  Business records include correspondence regarding personnel and transactions with banks, advertisers, printers, engravers, and other companies with which Tiger's Eye did business. It also includes bank statements, financial and subscription ledgers, and calendars documenting the receipt and return of material for the magazine. Financial documents concerning trust funds for Ruth Stephan's children by her first marriage are also present.
  - Financial Papers
    - Personnel - correspondence, etc., 1947-1950; 4 (Box 34)
    - Business correspondence - miscellaneous estimates, etc., 1946-1947 (Box 34)
    - Accounting - reports and correspondence, 1947-1951; 2 (Box 34)
    - Accounts payable, 1949 (Box 34)
    - Advertising and publicity
      - Advertising copy, 1948-1949; 2 (Box 34)
      - Advertising copy (to go out), 1948-1949 (Box 34)
      - Dead file, 1947-1948 (Box 34)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 34)
      - Miscellaneous back issue advance, data, etc., 1945-1949 (Box 34)
      - Proposed lists, 1947-1949; 2 (Box 34)
      - Prospective advertisers: correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 35)
      - Rate cards, etc., 1947-1949 (Box 35)
      - Unpaid bills, 1949 (Box 35)
    - Announcements and promotional data, 1947-1949 (Box 35)
    - Banks - miscellaneous correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 35)
    - Bank deposit slips - entered, 1951 (Box 35)
    - Bank advices, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
    - Company files
      - Addison Gallery of American Art, 1948 October (Box 35)
      - Alan Swallow, Publisher, 1947-1949 (Box 35)
      - American Trade Press Clipping Bureau, 1949 November 1 (Box 35)
      - Banyan Press, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Benevy, Herbert; frames, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Betty Parsons Gallery, 1947-1948 (Box 35)
      - Bocour Colors, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Briggs, H. E. (Books 'N Things), 1947-1949 (Box 35)
      - Buchholz Gallery - Curt Valentin, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Cage, John, 1948 January 4 (Box 35)
      - Contour Quarterly, undated (Box 35)
      - Creative Age Press, 1949 (Box 35)
      - Cronos, 1948 (Box 35)
      - Cummington Press, 1948 (Box 35)
      - Duell Sloane & Pearce, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Durlacher Brothers Gallery, 1948 January 4 (Box 35)
      - E. P. Dutton & Co., 1947-1948 (Box 35)
      - The Elm Tree Press (Rudge, William Edwin), 1947-1948; 2 (Box 35)
      - Four Seasons Book Shop, 1948 January 13 (Box 35)
      - Furioso, 1947-1948 (Box 35)
      - Golden Goose Press, 1949 (Box 35)
      - Gotham Book Mart, 1948 February 2 (Box 35)
      - Guide-Kalkhoff-Burr, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 35)
      - Here And Now, 1947-1949 (Box 35)
      - Herman N. Stevens Agency, 1949-1950 (Box 35)
      - The Holliday Bookshop, 1948 November (Box 35)
      - Inventario, 1947-1948 (Box 35)
      - Julien Levy Gallery, 1947-1948 (Box 35)
      - K Editeur, 1948 (Box 35)
      - Kleeman Galleries, 1948 (Box 35)
      - Knoedler Gallery, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Las Moradas, 1948-1949 (Box 35)
      - Magazine of Art, 1947-1948 (Box 35)
      - MacMillan Company, 1947-1950 (Box 36)
      - Neurotica, 1948 (Box 36)
      - New Directions, 1947-1949 (Box 36)
      - New Mexico Quarterly Review, 1948 January (Box 36)
      - Padell Publishers, 1947-1948 (Box 36)
      - Paris Theatre, 1949 (Box 36)
      - Peerless, 1949 September 14 (Box 36)
      - Peerless Photo Engraving, 1947-1949; 5 (Box 36)
      - Perls Galleries, 1947-1948 (Box 36)
      - Pierre Berès, Inc., 1949 (Box 36)
      - Pierre Matisse Gallery, 1947-1949 (Box 36)
      - Poetry Magazine, 1947-1949 (Box 36)
      - Press Eight (Wheeler, Steve), 1949 (Box 36)
      - Quadrangle Press, 1947-1949 (Box 36)
      - Reinhold-Gould, Inc. (paper), 1947-1949 (Box 36)
      - Sewanee Review, 1947-1949 (Box 36)
      - Stevens-Nelson Paper Corporation, 1949 September 14 (Box 36)
      - Transition Press, 1948 November (Box 36)
      - Weyhe, E., 1948-1949 (Box 36)
      - Willard Gallery, 1947-1949 (Box 36)
    - Copyright assignments, permissions, loans, etc., 1947-1951 (Box 36)
    - Copyright permissions, etc., 1947-1950 (Box 36)
    - Copyright certificates and correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 37)
    - Debits for foreign payments, 1948, 1950 (Box 37)
    - Engraving companies - miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 37)
    - Exchange magazines, 1949-1950 (Box 37)
    - List of exchanges, 1949 (Box 37)
    - Exchange advertisements, 1949 (Box 37)
    - Exchange magazines - miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 37)
    - Foundations, 1949 December (Box 37)
    - Inventory, 1949-1951 (Box 37)
    - Legal documents, 1947-1948 (Box 37)
    - Legal - miscellaneous correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 37)
    - Library letter, 1949 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and bills - office equipment, running expenses, etc., 1947-1951 (Box 37)
    - 1948 returns from booksellers - sample copy list, rejections, 3 (Box 37)
    - Outgoing advance notes, 1950 January, undated (Box 37)
    - Paper companies - miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 37)
    - Parcel post, 1950-1951 (Box 37)
    - Part time help, 1949-1950 (Box 37)
    - Payroll records, 1949-1950 (Box 37)
    - Personnel, 1951 (Box 38)
    - Petty cash, 1949-1951; 3 (Box 38)
    - Post Office - correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 38)
    - Postal receipts, 1947-1949; 2 (Box 38)
    - Proofreader marks and proof in and out chart, undated (Box 38)
    - Publicity clippings, 1947-1948; 2 (Box 38)
    - Receipted bills, 1947-1951; 5 (Box 38)
    - Receipts, 1947-1948 (Box 39)
    - Stationery, undated; 4 (Box 39)
    - Tax information, 1950-1951; 2 (Box 39)
    - Taxes, 1947-1951 (Box 39)
    - Trust Report for Peter Walgreen Dart, 1941-1953; 3 (Box 40)
    - Trust Report for Justin W. Dart, Jr., 1942-1953; 3 (Box 40)
    - Checks, 1947-1950; 10 (Box 41-42)
    - Cancelled checks, 1951 April; 4 (Box 42)
    - Bank deposit slips, 1947-1950; 7 (Box 42-44)
    - Bank statements, 1947-1955; 8 (Box 44)
  - Subscription Files
    - Individual subscriber ledger sheets (A-R), [1947-1948]; 6 (Box 45)
    - Individual subscriber ledger sheets (S-Z), [1947-1948]; 3 (Box 46)
    - Individual subscriber ledger sheets (A-K), [1949-1951]; 4 (Box 46)
    - Individual subscriber ledger sheets (L-Z, foreign), [1949-1951]; 5 (Box 47)
    - Dealer transaction files, [1947-1951]; 4 (Box 48)
  - Record Books
    - Address book (2), 1948, undated; 2 (Box 49)
    - Annual diary (2), 1948; 2 (Box 49)
    - Annual diary, 1949-1951; 3 (Box 49-50)
    - Calendar pad, 1947; 2 (Box 50)
    - Check books (4), 1947-1951
    - Day calendar, 1947 (Box 50)
    - Day calendar, 1949-1950; 3 (Box 50)
    - Inventory notebook, undated (Box 51)
    - Ledger - cash receipts journal, 1947-1951
    - Ledger - expenses (2), 1947, undated; 2 (Box 51)
    - Ledger - financial (2), 1946-1951
    - Memo book, undated; 3 (Box 51)
    - Note pad (blank), undated (Box 51)
    - Steno pad, undated (Box 51)
- Series V: 1971 Addition, 1946-1951; 0.84; (2 boxes)
  Series V consists of correspondence, manuscripts, and notes that were not included in the original gift.
  - Author submissions, 1948-1950; 5 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence - manuscript requests, [1949] (Box 52)
  - Harmon, Catherine, 1949-1951 (Box 52)
  - Hyman, ______ (manuscript), 1947 October 25 (Box 52)
  - Letters returned to sender, 1948-1951; 2 (Box 52)
  - Lye, Len, "The Identity of Value", 1951 August (Box 53)
  - Manuscript - A Short Introduction to the Indian Dance Through the Art of Ram Gopal, by Churton Fairman, undated; 2 (Box 53)
  - Manuscripts for translation, 1946 June, undated (Box 53)
  - Manuscripts on query, undated (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1947-1949; 2 (Box 53)
  - Notes for prospective issues, undated (Box 53)
  - Untitled manuscript by Owen P. Griffiths, undated; 2 (Box 53)
- Oversize, 0.75; (4 boxes)
  - Check books (4) (In Series IV), 1947-1951; 4 (Box 54-55)
  - Ledger - cash receipts journal (In Series IV), 1947-1951 (Box 56)
  - Ledger - financial (2) (In Series IV), 1946-1951; 2 (Box 56)
  - Overmatter (In Series III), undated (Box 57)
  - Page proof - complete set (In Series III), 1949 June, undated; 2 (Box 57)